Shih-Ting Huang

User Experience Designer

www.shihting-huang.com (734) 882-8716 stingh@umich.edu

FEATURED UX PROJECTS

CureBack UX Designer Ann Arbor, MI, Sep - Dec 2018
Designed a personal rehabilitative exercise mobile app to help chronic back pain maintain compliance with a home exercise program.

AnleneMove UX ResearcherSingapore, May - Jul 2015
Conducted a 21-day diary study to enhance the user engagement of a health habit-forming mobile application. Tracked, analyzed, and created a usability optimizing report on a study of voice mail interview.

Social Profiler Design LeadTaipei, Taiwan, Mar - May 2016

Led a team of four to design a social analytics online tool that helps
marketer gain insights of social media users; identified user needs through
persona, wireframed the interfaces of product website and dashboard, and
tested the usability through prototypes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UMSI

Research ConsultantAnn Arbor, MI, Sep - Dec 2018
Consulted on improving outpatient scheduling information process at
Briarwood Family Clinic; conducted a contextual inquiry of the stakeholders; crafted an in-depth analysis report on streamlining the patient scheduling.

Ogilvy

Senior Digital ConsultantTaipei, Taiwan, Sep 2015- Dec 2017
Consulted on digital-focused rebranding and new digital product development: conducted industrial and competitor survey; positioned key platforms tasks among digital ecosystem; delivered digital go-to-market plan and brand revitalization suggestions of the contents, usability, and brand tonality on digital platforms. Key clients: *CommonWealth Magazine* and *Dynacomware*- a Font Company in Taiwan.

Senior Social Media Planner Taipei, Taiwan, Mar 2014 - Feb 2015 Led a team of four to pitch 15+ potential clients, helping grow the division by 400% YOY; developed digital marketing communication and social media strategies for 20+ global brands. Key clients: Adidas, Mercedes-Benz, Nestle Dolce Gusto.

Conceptualized and wireframed a gaming web app on Facebook and designed engaging social content for "Adidas Crazy Light 2" campaign; generated 60,000 shares and 1.2 million total impressions.

EDUCATION

University of Michigan Ann Arbor, MI

M.S. Health Informatics, specializing in UX design School of Information and School of Public Health Sep 2018 - Apr 2020

National Chengchi University

B.A. Economics, Taiwan Sep 2006 - Jun 2011

University of Cologne

Exchange Program Germany, Feb 2010 - Jun 2010

SKILLS

Design

Interaction Design Wireframing Rapid Prototyping

Research

Competitive Analysis
Usability Testing
Contextual Inquiry
Interviews/Survey
Persona / Journey Mapping
Social Media & Web Analysis

Tools

Photoshop Sketch Axure Marvel Invision

Languages

Professional English, Chinese(Native)

AWARDS

2019 Design Jam The Library of the Great Lakes (First Place)